Contact

contact@mahdiroudaki.info

www.linkedin.com/in/mahdiroudaki (LinkedIn) mahdiroudaki.info (Personal)

Top Skills

C++

Qt Creator

Full-Stack Web Developement

Languages

Persian (Native or Bilingual)

English (Professional Working)

Turkish (Limited Working)

Certifications

Site Development Associate Certificate in Advanced English

Honors-Awards

Participate in RoboCup IranOpen - UAV League

Mahdi Roudaki

Software Engineer at HANA Systems Company Iran

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer skilled in Designing and Developing Web Applications. Also I have a good knowledge as a Qt and C ++ Developer. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Software Engineering from Islamic Azad University.

Experience

Tehran Province, Iran

Houshmand Afzar Negar Aseman (HANA) Qt Developer January 2019 - Present

Houshmand Afzar Negar Aseman (HANA) C++ Developer January 2019 - Present Tehran Province, Iran

Houshmand Afzar Negar Aseman (HANA) Software Engineer January 2019 - Present Tehran Province, Iran

Robotic Research Laboratory (R2Lab) Software Engineer January 2016 - Present Tehran Province, Iran

Education

Islamic Azad University
Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering (2016 - 2020)

Lavasani Dana High School Diploma, Mathematics · (2012 - 2015)